<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>You don't start out writing good stuff on ABJ IT</title><link>https://abjit.dk/</link><description>Recent content in You don't start out writing good stuff on ABJ IT</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 16:12:08 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abjit.dk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Run Jenkins on K8s</title><link>https://abjit.dk/posts/run-jenkins-on-k8s/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 16:12:08 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://abjit.dk/posts/run-jenkins-on-k8s/</guid><description>Enabling Jenkins to use k8s pods as build nodes This is the first post about how to configure Jenkins to utilize Kubernetes Pods as build slaves.
The goal of the blog post is to run a simple job, specified with a Jenkinsfile, on a dynamically created pods in Kubernetes.
prereqs. A running Jenkins A running Kubernetes cluster</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://abjit.dk/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abjit.dk/pages/about/</guid><description>Contra vagos Lorem markdownum notam si lintea meque certa en meumque illis, diu fatigant, nec praedae concustodita arcet. Paviunt castris cur errat ventis causa! Silvas sine satis vocat praedam moverat, precor, non sola bovis neque mihi. Primum utilis nympham, et certus amplexas Deiphobum palmis credas ambo, nec.
Excidit gente, si orat suo quaeque dura Calydon nata? Pars auro post stetit adfusique imis amplexus. Agmina per fabricator mittere Erymanthon habetque tot.</description></item><item><title>CV</title><link>https://abjit.dk/pages/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abjit.dk/pages/cv/</guid><description>This is raw HTML, inside Markdown. Consultant Work Jun 2015 - Aug 2017: Student Developer @ Schantz Part of the internal Build and Deploy team (aka devops), where task includes all parts of the CI/CD pipelines and flows. Also helping developers debug pipelines and code issues.
Tools and technologies:
Jenkins
Git
Java
Groovy
Python
Jan 2014 - Jun 2015: IT Support Assistant @ Schantz
Helping out in the internal IT support team.</description></item></channel></rss>