<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome on ABJ IT</title><link>https://abjit.dk/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome on ABJ IT</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 16:12:08 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abjit.dk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Run Jenkins on K8s</title><link>https://abjit.dk/posts/run-jenkins-on-k8s/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 16:12:08 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://abjit.dk/posts/run-jenkins-on-k8s/</guid><description>Enabling Jenkins to use k8s pods as build nodes This is the first post about how to configure Jenkins to utilize Kubernetes Pods as build slaves.
The goal of the blog post is to run a simple job, specified with a Jenkinsfile, on a dynamically created pods in Kubernetes.
prereqs. A running Jenkins A running Kubernetes cluster</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://abjit.dk/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abjit.dk/pages/about/</guid><description>About A devops enginner that turned to freelancing to take on diverse and exciting projects for clients, big and small. Super interested in start-ups and always on the look out for a potential early stage startup to join or help out. I&amp;rsquo;m big of fan of remote work and always do my best to provide clear communication, verbally and written.
My work and interests mainly focuses on DevOps related tools such as CI/CD engines (Jenkins, Gitlab, Github etc.</description></item><item><title>CV</title><link>https://abjit.dk/pages/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abjit.dk/pages/cv/</guid><description>Work DevOps Engineer (freelance) Mar 2022 - Present
Shure Nordic
Brought into the globally distributed internal Devops Team to provide general help and support with CI &amp;amp; CD tasks and specfically improve and scale their internal build (CI) capacity using AWS. The team also needed help getting started using EKS and Kubernetes in general, which I also provided.
Tools and technologies: Jenkins, Python, EKS, NPM, Bitbucket, Confluence &amp;amp; Jira</description></item></channel></rss>